Michael Borer

Denver, CO 80212 mpborer@gmail.com +1 303 809 1559

Professional Summary

Attentive Manager and Technician with the training and motivation required to lead the shop to safe and proper repairs of vehicles. Adept at providing an optimal level of customer support that includes speedy resolutions to customer service issues. Specialize in managing an able staff to meet customer expectations. Ensured customer satisfaction and retention through the direction of shop staff in the performance of quality vehicle repair and maintenance services.

Work Experience

Ground Service Mechanic

PrimeFlight Aviation-Denver, CO October 2023 to April 2024

- · Work directly with supervisors and QC team to determine downed units and prioritize repairs.
- inspect power units weekly to ensure proper running condition when needed.
- complete annual inspections and repairs.
- complete breakdown repairs on all fueling equipment.

Automotive Technician

Barbee's Freeway Ford-Denver, CO October 2022 to April 2023

- Work with service writer and management to diagnose vehicle needs and customer complaints.
- Repair vehicles based upon customer approvals and repair industry standards and service manuals.
- Complete warranty repairs and associated paperwork to submit to Ford for approvals and payments.

Automotive Technician

Ford Motor Company-Lakewood, CO December 2020 to January 2022

- Work with service writer and management to diagnose vehicle needs and customer complaints.
- Repair vehicles based upon customer approvals and repair industry standards and service manuals.
- Complete warranty repairs and associated paperwork to submit to Ford for approvals and payments.

Shift Supervisor

Ryder-Denver, CO May 2017 to April 2020

- -Ensure positive customer relationships, including issue resolutions, customer satisfaction and retention
- -Responsible for work analysis, planning and scheduling, assigning work to technicians, productivity tracking and optimization
- -Maintain a safe and clean service environment, while maintaining equipment and facility

Assistant General Manager

Travel Centers of America-Commerce City, CO September 2016 to May 2017

- -Supervised 6 bay service facility, 3 service trucks and mobile maintenance truck
- -Scheduled technicians to meet repair service appointments, assisting with daily work routines
- -Receive and control inventory, pay bills and create PO logs for bookkeeping
- -Supervised and provided guidance to technicians

Diesel Mechanic

Travel Centers of America-Wheat Ridge, CO March 2012 to September 2016

- -Tech level 1 progressed to tech level 5
- -Mentor Technician
- -Assisted in everyday work operations and help aid in work flow

Education

MMI

Motorcycle Mechanics Institute - Phoenix, AZ May 2010 to May 2010

Skills

- Electrical experience
- Automotive Repair
- Mechanic Experience
- · Commercial driving
- Vehicle Maintenance